各位圣诞节快乐
Merry crap-mas, everyone.
太无聊了
This sucks.
好吧 孩子们
Okay, guys.
我知道这个圣诞节没能按我们的计划进行
I know christmas didn't go exactly how we planned.
我们的圣诞树下没有礼物
We don't have any presents under the tree.
- 我们连树都没有 - 但是圣诞老人
- We don't have a tree. - But santa...
圣诞老人打电话过来说他今年不能来了
Santa called. He's not gonna be able to make it this year.
但关键是 我们还在一起
But here's the thing... we have each other.
我们又一起走过了一年 那才是真正重要的
We got through another year together, and that's what really matters.
- 耶 没有人挂掉 - 真心圣诞快乐啊
- Yay, none of us died. - Merry christmas.
所以我们这样 行吗
So this is what we're gonna do, okay?
我们下楼 然后充分享受这段时光
We're gonna go downstairs, and we are gonna make the best of this.
怎么样 走吧
All right? Let's go.
动起来
Come on.
神赐福我们 各位
God bless us, every one!
☆☆☆果然字幕组出品 www.grimmfan.com☆☆☆
外星邻居 第 1 季 第 9 集
翻译 CeiCei 毛毛 小P 土豆
校对 Morri 木易 小虫妖妖  时间 鸡腿  后期 芒果果
字幕片源来自网络 仅供学习交流 版权归原公司所有
你帮Max买了Ipad了吗 我想我们忘了买Ipad了
Did you get Max's Ipad? I think we forgot the Ipad.
我们没忘 就在这里
We didn't forget it. It's right there.
- 用蓝色包装纸包的这个 - 你确定那个装的是Ipad吗
- It's the blue wrapping paper. - Are you sure that's the Ipad?
亲爱的 你一般都会记得你给你8岁的孩子买了什么
Honey, you tend to remember something you bought your 8-year-old
如果你接下来三年都要为它分期还款的话
that you're gonna be paying for for the next three years.
好吧 我买了Amber的滑雪板 购物单上的东西买齐了
Okay, I got Amber's snowboard, and our list is officially complete.
其他的就交给圣诞老人了
The rest is up to Santa.
好嘞
Ho!
- 哈喽 - 嘿 你们好
- Hello! - Hey, guys!
怎么穿着围裙呢 在做饭吗
What's with the apron? You cooking something?
不 我只是喜欢它的修身功能
No. I just like what it does for my silhouette.
他超爱围裙的
He loves the apron.
是这样的 需要你们帮个小忙
So, guys, we need a small favor.
我们需要藏圣诞礼物的地方
We need a place to hide our christmas gifts.
我们有一窝嗅觉敏锐的孩子 然后
We got some nosy kids, and...
圣诞节耶 我一直都对这个感到兴奋不已的
Christmas! I've been so excited for this one!
哦 你们人类
Oh, you people.
所以说 我们对这个也不应该感到兴奋吗
So, we're not excited about this one, either?
- 他又要开始了 - 你是说我从3月起就一直听到的
- Here we go. - You mean the orgy of commercialism
商业狂欢么 我想不是
I've been hearing about since March? No.
我只是不明白两个相对理智的人类
I just don't see how two relatively sane human beings
会参与到这么不理智的节日中
can participate in such an insane holiday.
哦 这没有不理智 Larry 这给我们
Oh, it's not insane, Larry. It's fun for us,
和孩子们带来快乐 而且Abby现在6岁
and for the kids, and Abby's 6,
她还陷在圣诞的魔法之中无法自拔呢
and she still gets caught up in the magic of it all.
啊 又是这个 Abby 老是关于Abby
Ah, there it is. Abby. It's always about "Abby."
别在我女儿名字上加引号 Larry
Don't put my daughter in quotations, Larry.
那个小女孩有什么特别的吗 就我看来 一点都没有
What's so special about that little girl? Nothing, as far as I can see.
你们却编造了另一个借口
Yet you two have concocted yet another excuse
将一次性的商业垃圾
to lavish both her and the more worthwhile Weaver children
塞给她和Weaver家其他更好的孩子
with disposable commercial crap.
- Larry 你完全理解了 - 听着 圣诞节是一个家庭的事
- Larry, you've got it all wrong. - Okay, christmas is about family
是大家在一起欢笑 享受彼此的陪伴
and smiles and the joy of being together.
礼物只是个很小的部分
The gifts are just one tiny part of it.
哦 是啊 然后还有一个浑身是膘 邋里邋遢的入室窃贼
Oh, yes. And there's that fat, slovenly burglar
你们叫他作圣诞老人 说句心里话
you call Santa Claus. Honestly.
看在上帝份上 穿个围裙吧 胖子
Put on an apron for god's sake, fatso.
他和圣诞老人杠上了
He's struggling with Santa Claus.
当然你们可以把礼物放在我们这儿
Of course you can keep your presents here.
- 好的 绕到背后去 - 准备好了吗 亲爱的
- All right, get around back. - Ready, babe?
- 1... 2... - 小心上面
- 1... 2... - Watch the top.
- 推着你装满垃圾的手推车进来吧 - 我没事
- Wheel your barrow your full of crap... - I'm okay.
门 门
The door. The door.
掉下来了 掉下来了
Man down. Man down.
没事 好了 我接住了
All right. Yeah, we got it.
小心着点地板 那是竹制的
Just watch the floors. They're bamboo.
好的 没问题了
I got it. Yes. Okay.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你觉得Larry说的对吗 也许我们太在意于礼物了
Do you think Larry's right, and we're too caught up in the presents?
不 亲爱的 Larry那只是本性难移 懂吗
No, babe. Larry's just being Larry, okay?
我们的孩子知道圣诞节的意义
Our kids understand the meaning of christmas.
他们甚至不需要礼物
They don't even need presents.
嘿 老妈 确认下我的滑雪板是要有穿入式固定装置的 不是傻乎乎的搭扣式的
Hey, mom, make sure my snowboard has step-in bindings and not those lame straps.
那要看圣诞老人带来的是什么了
We'll see what Santa brings.
好吧 也用不着操心包装了
Yeah, uh, don't even worry about wrapping it.
那只会是浪费时间
It's just gonna slow me down.
还有 Jeremy打电话来 说是
Also, Jeremy called, and it turns out
我们那个滑雪旅行从圣诞后一天改到
we're going on the ski trip the day before christmas
圣诞前一天了 所以我要早点拿到礼物
instead of the day after, so I'm gonna need my presents early.
等一下 Amber
Hold up, Amber.
- 我们一家人要一起过这个圣诞节 - 是啊
- This family celebrates christmas together. - Yeah.
好 我会在山上给你们发短信的
Yeah. I'll text you from the mountain.
什么啊
What...
没事 我还在呢
Well, I'll be here.
我还想要些新Xbox游戏
And I want some new games for the Xbox.
等等 我还以为你要ipad
Wait. I thought you wanted an Ipad.
我都要 对了 我还想要辆新自行车
I'll multitask. Oh, and I also want a new bike.
一辆新的自行车 你呢
A new bike. What about you, huh?
你需要做些改动吗
You have any changes you'd like to make?
不麻烦了 Santa知道我想要什么 他会准备好的
Nah. Santa knows what I want. He'll take care of me.
对了 这是我新的愿望清单
Oh, and, uh, here's my new list.
我把有变动的地方特别标出来了
I've highlighted the changes.
一定要注意看第三页
Be sure to look at page 3.
第三页
Page 3.
你应该发传真给圣诞老人 时间不多了
You should probably fax it. It's getting pretty late.
好的 我就去 谢谢
Okay, I'll get on that. Thank you.
天啊 怎么回事 这难道是宪法吗
God! What the hell? Is this the constitution?
谁会给圣诞节礼物单写修正案啊
Who makes amendments to a christmas list?
你知道吗 你说的没错
You know what? You're right.
他们只在乎圣诞礼物 孩子们都疯了
It's become all about this stuff. Our kids are completely out of control.
我恨他们三个熊孩子 Marty
I hated all three of them just now, Marty.
那一刻 我恨他们三个
In that moment, I hated all three of our children.
嘿
You know what?
也许我们今年可以过个与众不同的圣诞
Maybe we should try something different this year.
别管那些礼物了
Forget the presents.
我们去哪儿度个假吧
Let's take a nice vacation somewhere
和家人一起过圣诞节
and hang with the family for christmas.
去个好点的地方 去热带的某个地方
Somewhere nice. Maybe somewhere tropical.
不错 但我们去不起热带啊
Yeah, but we can't afford tropical.
买那堆礼物花了一大笔钱呢
We just spent a buttload of money on all their presents.
我们把礼物退掉 拿这笔钱去旅游
No! We return the presents and we use the money for the trip!
- 我们可以这么做吗 - 我们可是家长
- Can we do that? - We're the parents.
我们可是给这帮贪心的小妖孽取名字的人
We named those greedy little monsters.
- 我们想怎样就怎样 - 我的天
- We can do whatever we want! - Oh, my god!
我们可以在圣诞节晒成古铜色了
We could have christmas tans.
超级碗的时候我就是古铜色的啦
I'm gonna be brown for the super bowl!
看看这一大堆实体化了的消费主义
Look at this bloated pile of consumerism.
大部分还都是给那个小姑娘的
And most of it for that little girl.
她是什么情况 她真有这么可爱吗
What's her deal? Is she really that cute?
老公 她可可爱了
She is pretty cute, husband.
老爸 她可以说是我见过的最可爱的小孩了
Dad, she's pretty much the cutest kid ever.
她还一直在掉牙
And her teeth keep on falling out of her face.
接下来要掉什么 鼻子么
What's gonna fall off next, her nose?
老爸 我超爱听你吐槽小孩子的
Oh, father! I love it when you make fun of children.
这一切都很可笑
The whole thing is ridiculous. I mean,
什么东西能长成这样
what could possibly be this shape,
还让收到的人觉得很高兴呢
and yet be so exciting to receive?
刚刚不是在反问 我是真的在问问题
No, really. It's not a rhetorical question.
- 你觉得这是什么 - 它看起来像一块巨大的板
- What do you think it is? - It looks like a giant board,
可能是某种冬季运动用的
perhaps for some sort of, um, winter sport.
别傻了 Reggie
Don't be a dolt, Reggie.
到底是什么惊喜
What's the surprise?
我和你们的爸爸经过讨论
Well, your dad and I were talking,
决定今年要过一个与往年不同的圣诞节
And we decided to do christmas a little different this year.
提前发礼物 不
Presents early? No.
我们可以过犹太式圣诞然后连着八天拿礼物吗
Can we do jewish christmas and get presents for eight days?
不不 我们决定今年不发礼物了 改成
What? No. We decided that instead of presents this year...
全家去旅游
We're going on a family trip!
我们没有在开玩笑
We're not joking.
他们没有在开玩笑
They're not joking!
你们没有在开玩笑吗
You're not joking?
你们在玩什么烂把戏
What kind of sick game are you playing?
我们还只是孩子呢
We're just children!
也许这是一只加拉帕戈斯群岛上的陆龟 它的壳是平的
Perhaps it's a galapagos turtle with a flattened shell.
一把巨型枪
A giant stick of gum?
好吧 再问一下 为什么我们这么快就把滑雪板否定了
Okay, one more time, why are we so quick to dismiss snowboard?
哦我的天
Oh, my.
这感觉实在太好了
Oh, that felt really, really good.
太美妙了
It's beautiful.
- 老公 这是什么 - 这是 这是
- What is it, husband? - It's a... it's... it's...
这是一样东西
It's a thing.
- 它美妙极了 - 它就像它看起来那么好玩吗
- And it's glorious. - Okay, was that as fun as it looked?
也许更好玩
Even better.
- 我想要 - 我也要
- I want one! - Me, too!
没问题 人人有份
Yes! Presents for everyone!
我拿到了自行车 真棒
I got a bike! Cool!
圣诞节最棒了
Christmas is the best thing ever!
耶
Yeah!
所以今年圣诞节没有礼物了
So no presents for christmas this year?
很好 你们毁了圣诞节 一年中唯一一个我认为这个家庭还可以忍受的日子
Great. You've ruined the one day a year I actually find this family tolerable.
我们说清楚
So just to be clear,
我一整年都很乖
I've been good all year,
我却要和她归在一起么
and I'm getting lumped in with her?
好吧 我猜全家旅行也挺有意思
Well, I guess a trip for the family sounds fun.
哦 闭嘴 马屁精
Oh, zip it, kiss-ass.
你说过我可以和Jeremy一起去旅行
You already told me I could go on a trip with Jeremy.
好吧 我觉得我们都忘记了圣诞节的真正意义
Okay. I think we've all lost sight of what christmas is really about.
意义不在于礼物
It is not about presents.
而在于团聚
It's about being together,
我们要全家一起出动 所有人一起
and we are gonna go away as a family, all of us.
这是不是意味着我们得把给你们的礼物退回呢
Does this mean we have to return the presents we got for you?
你给我们买了礼物
You got us presents?
当然没有 但你知道那是什么感觉了
Of course not, but do you see how that feels?
妈妈 我很困惑
Mommy, I'm confused.
我在购物中心看到圣诞老人了
I saw Santa at the mall,
他说我今年很乖
and he said I was very good this year,
我会得到想要的一切
and I would be getting everything I asked for.
哦 别担心 亲爱的
Well, don't worry about that, sweetie,
因为爸爸今早一直在和圣诞老人发短信 猜猜说了什么
because daddy was texting back and forth with Santa this morning, and guess what?
-他批准了我们的旅行  -知道么 这很有趣
- He approved our trip!  - You know what? That's interesting,
因为在你与圣诞老人发完短信后 我还和他视频来着
Because I was skype-ing with Santa after you finished texting with him,
他说我可以和我的朋友一起去滑雪行
and he said that I could go on a ski trip with my friends.
什么
What?
我也认识圣诞老人
I know Santa, too.
好吧 你知道么 鬼灵精
All right. You know what, smart-mouth?
让我声明一下
Let me be really clear.
你不许去什么滑雪行
You are not going on your ski trip.
真逊
So lame.
来吧 伙计们 回房间吧 趁他们没把房间也收走
Come on, guys. Let's go to our rooms before they take those away, too.
能再提醒我下么 为什么想要与这些孩子在岛上独处
Can you remind me again why want to be alone on island with these children?
这圣诞电影真是个精彩的故事
That Christmas movie is a wonderful story.
我爱这个幽灵
I love the ghost.
同意 尽管我不喜欢小Tim
Agreed. Although I didn't like tiny Tim.
小只 诡异 完全不搭情节
Little, weird, and totally unrelatable.
我承认 我对圣诞节的看法错了
I admit it. I was wrong about christmas.
这是个可爱的节日
It's a lovely holiday.
这些东西 树啦 雪啦
The things, the trees, the snow.
那些东西
The things.
圣诞节充满魔力 父亲 魔力
Christmas is magical, father! Magical!
Dick Dick 伸直你的膝盖
Dick, Dick, fix your joints.
你会肚子痛的
You're going to get a bellyache.
但我还是无法对圣诞老人那个家伙释怀
I still can't get past that Santa fellow, though.
5.26亿儿童庆祝圣诞节
526 million children celebrate christmas.
意味着他每小时要送礼物
That means he has to deliver presents
给2200万儿童
to 22 million children an hour.
我是说 真的
I mean, really!
我们假设他在一晚上就环游世界
I mean, we're saying he gets around the whole world in one night...
还胖成那样
at that weight.
我说 他都挤不进雪橇了
I mean, he can't fit into a sleigh,
更别说驾雪橇飞了
Let alone fly in one.
抱歉 我知道跑题了
I'm sorry. I know this is off topic,
但是这玩意我穿对了吧
but is anyone gonna admit that I got this right?
没有
No.
要不然
Tell you what.
我们再看一遍 圣诞颂歌木偶剧
Let's watch "The Muppets: A christmas carol" again.
我喜欢木偶
The Muppets I like.
我还能学得很像
I could really get down with the muppets.
Kermit
Kermit.
Jackie Joyner-Kersee
Jackie Joyner-Kersee,
请按play键
please press "play."
-好极了  -看到没有
- That was very good! - Did you see that?
-是的  -我知道 非常好
- Yes. - I know, it's awfully good.
非常好
Very good.
哦 我找好了 Marty 看这个
Oh, I got it, Marty. Look at this...
享受夏威夷时光 可预订
"available time-share in hawaii.
三间卧室 新潮厨房 海滩步行可及 装有坐浴盆
"three bedrooms, updated kitchen,
short walk to the beach, bidet"!
传说中洗屁屁的玩意
The tushie-squirting thing?
天哪 他们还有专门洗屁屁的浴盆
Holy crap, they have the tushie-squirting thing!
等下 等下 我们预算够吗
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Can we afford this?
在我们的接受范围内 Marty 就是它了
It's in our price range. Marty, this is ours!
我们可以的 我们要去夏威夷
We can do this! We're going to hawaii!
-是的  -我们去拿礼物再退回去
- Yeah! - Oh, let's go get the gifts and return them
-这样我们就能付得起了  -我的屁股已经感觉到潮湿了
- so we can pay for this thing. - My tushie feels wet already.
祝我圣诞快乐
Merry christmas to me.
之前我真是大错特错了
I have never been so wrong about anything in my life.
我爱圣诞节
I love christmas!
Larry 你出什么事了
Larry, what the hell is the matter with you?
自来在这蠢星球上起 第一次没出事
For the first time on this stupid planet, nothing.
我沉浸在快乐中 脑海里充满了甜蜜
I'm totally joyous. I have sugarplums in my head!
怎么 你出什么事了
Why? What's the matter with you?
你应该帮我们看管好礼物
You were supposed to hold on to our gifts
管几天 而不把它们送掉
for a few days, not give them away!
-也不是摧毁它们  -圣诞快乐
- Or destroy 'em! - Merry christmas!
我不敢相信居然发生了这种事
I can't believe this is happening.
说实话 我觉得你们做事完全不靠谱
To be honest, I think you're being completely illogical
就像龌龊的小妖精
and a bit of a nasty elf.
你说过 圣诞节就是给予
You said christmas is about giving.
我不会让你毁了我的圣诞节 绝不会
I won't let you ruin christmas for me. I just won't!
你说什么 我们毁了你的圣诞节
I'm sorry. We're ruining your christmas?!
你把我们的礼物送了出去
You gave our gifts away!
那些外星人为什么在玩我们的礼物
Why are the aliens playing with our presents?
他们是在扔我的Ipad吗
Are they throwing my Ipad?
Jackie 这回真是惹大祸了
Jackie, this is a major screw-up.
哦 不 又来了
Oh, no, not again.
你们真是有太多节日能让我们糟蹋了
It's just that you have so many holidays　for us to screw up.
我们能不能直接跳到一切完美结局以后
Can't we just get to the part　where everything ends up being all right
我们开始相互学习的那一部分
and we learn　from one another?
-不能那样吗  -Jackie 我们攒了一年的钱才买到这些
- Can't we do that?　- Jackie, we save up all year for this.
可现在它们退不掉了 我们还要用退款去夏威夷呢
And now we can't return those gifts and use the money to go to hawaii!
真的很抱歉 我的丈夫不是故意
I'm so sorry. My husband didn't mean...
不要再替他道歉了 Jackie
Stop apologizing for him, Jackie.
你不能每次都替他犯的错道歉
You can't keep apologizing for him every time he makes a mistake
然后就不了了之
and expect everything to be better.
史上最糟圣诞节
Worst christmas ever!
期待一整年的一天就这么给搞砸了
Whole year of being good right down the crapper!
你真淘气 Bird先生
I'm afraid you've been naughty, Mr. Bird.
圣诞老人知道你什么时候调皮
And Santa knows when you've been naughty,
什么时候很乖
and he knows when you've been nice.
他知道健身房在哪儿吗
Does he know where the gym is?
因为他就快要因糖尿病截肢了
Because he's going to lose a foot to diabetes.
你好啊 我不起眼的小朋友
Hello, my little overlooked friend.
丈夫 我觉得我们真的犯了大错了
Husband, I think we've made a terrible mistake.
我们确实犯了大错了 我们漏了一个 哇
You bet your sweet bippy we did. We missed one. Ohh!
-全新Ipad  -丈夫
- The new Ipad! - Husband.
哦 没什么大不了的 那些东西
Oh, it's fine. It's just stuff
他们本来玩没两天就会腻的
They would have got bored with within a day or two.
但这个例外 乔布斯这个做的真是太赞了
But not this. Steve jobs really got it right with this one.
Larry Bird Weaver一家对我们一直都很好
Larry Bird! The Weavers have been so good to us,
可我们总是让他们失望
and we keep on disappointing them.
我们得弥补我们的错误
We have to make this right.
你要是不行动 那么我来
Either you do it, or I will.
等等 Jackie 你想要我做什么呢
Wait, Jackie.What do you want from me?
你是不是想要我送点花给他们  那样行吗
Do you want me to send them some flowers? Is that it?
Siri 我真的毁了他们的圣诞了吗
Siri, did I really ruin their christmas?
Siri
Siri?
我都不知道是怎样发生的
I don't even know how it happened.
只是看见那满地的包装纸和礼盒
Just seeing all that wrapping paper and boxes...
我知道你不会原谅我们了
I know you can't ever forgive us,
但是我们真的 真的为我们所做的一切感到很抱歉
but we are truly, truly sorry for what we did.
Jackie 你想要我说什么
Jackie, what do you want me to say?
我知道你们不是故意要伤害我们
I know you didn't mean to hurt us.
你们只是兴奋过头了 我了解
You guys got carried away.I get it.
你们在庆祝你们第一个圣诞
You celebrated your first christmas.
第一次总是最美好的
The first ones are always the best ones.
甚至对Amber也是
Even Amber.
她小时候过圣诞时 满脸都是甜蜜的兴奋
She had the sweetest look of excitement on her face her first few christmases.
每当她对我说出伤人的话时 我就回想那些记忆
I hang on to that memory when she says hurtful things to me.
呜
Ooh.
我猜你每天一定要回忆好多次
I imagine you must think of that several times a day.
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
随着孩子们一天天长大
With the kids all getting older,
我们很担心这是一家人一起迎接美妙早晨的
we were afraid that this was gonna be the last christmas where we'd have
最后一个圣诞节了
one of those magical mornings together.
Marty和我只是情难自已了
Marty and I just got carried away.
所以这次我们真的干坏事了
So we really screwed your pooch on this one.
噢 Jackie 你们不只是毁了这个圣诞
Oh, Jackie. Not only did you screw my pooch,
还深深伤了我们的心
but you didn't call her the next day, either.
这 很好喝
It's... Very good.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我一直在观察你
I've been watching you.
我看得出 你很难过
And I can tell you're sad.
所以我过来是想告诉你不要难过了
So I came over to tell you not to be sad,
因为圣诞老人会让一切都好起来的
cause Santa's going to make everything all better.
圣诞老人会让一切都好起来的
Santa's going to make everything all better.
我4岁的时候得了流感
When I was 4, I got the flu,
因此不能去见圣诞老人
So I coun't visit Santa.
我妈妈叫我写封信
So my mom told me to write a letter
她可以帮我在圣诞前寄给圣诞老人
so she could mail it to him before christmas.
从那以后 我一直在担心圣诞老人会把我忘了
The whole time, I was really worried that he had forgotten about me.
-可你猜怎么着  -怎么了
- But guess what? - What?
他给我回信了
He wrote me back.
噢 拜托
Oh, please.
他写了点啥
What did he write?
他要我即使在没人的时候 也要乖乖的
He reminded me to be good even when no one was watching,
永远不要忘记圣诞节的真谛
and to never forget what christmas is all about.
那是啥
What's that?
家人啊 白痴
Family, silly.
圣诞老人 这么跟你说的?
Santa... told you that?
所以别哭丧着脸了 Bird先生
So no more sad faces, Mr. Bird,
因为圣诞老人会让明天更美好的
'cause Santa's going to make everything all better.
他总会把问题解决的
He always comes through.
感谢您的款待 希望日后还有机会一起喝茶
Thank you for the tea. Let's do it again sometime.
哦 天啊
Oh, dear.
我真的是 真的太不懂事了
I've been very, very naughty.
天啊 你又想怎样
Oh, goodness. What are you up to now?
你是对的 老婆
You were right, wife.
Weaver一家一直对我们很好
The Weavers have been good to us,
所以我要补救这一切
so I'm going to make this right.
我要成为圣诞老爷爷 给他们一个完美的圣诞节
I'm going to be like Santa Claus and save their christmas.
我现在需要一个小精灵帮手 衣服我都已经准备好了
All I need is a helper elf. I've already made the costume.
噢 老公 你太棒了啦
Oh, husband, love of my life,
我永远是你的小精灵
I would be your elf any day.
快别傻了 你太高了
Don't be ridiculous. You're too tall.
我对事情的下一步发展甚为忧虑
Oh, I do not like where this is going.
我钱多的没处花 我想买辆车
I have a limitless amount cash and desire to buy a car.
头奖哎
Jackpot.
不好意思 你这个圣诞有什么计划么
Excuse me. Do you have any plans this christmas?
喔 我家人都死光了
Oh, my family's all dead.
太好了
Perfect.
完胜
Boo-yah!
抓住它 快跑儿子
Kept it. Move rapid, son.
抓住那只圣诞小猪
Capture the christmas swine!
抓最好看的那只
Get the pretty one!
- 剩蛋快乐 各位   - 好无聊啊
- Merry crap-mas, everyone.   - This sucks.
好了 伙计们
Okay, guys.
我知道圣诞和我们想象中的不太一样
I know christmas didn't go exactly how we planned.
- 圣诞树下没有礼物   - 我们连树都没有
- We don't have any presents under the tree.   - We don't have a tree.
我们现在这么办
So this is what we're gonna do, okay?
我们一起下楼
We're gonna go downstairs,
努力过个开心的圣诞节
and we are gonna make the best of this.
好吗  走吧
All right? Let's go.
来吧
Come on.
走
上帝保佑我们
God bless us, every one!
圣诞快乐 Weaver一家
Merry christmas, Weavers!
这是个什么情况
What the heck is going on?
我们知道你想要一个完美的圣诞节
Well, we know you wanted the perfect christmas...
我们知道你们想去夏威夷
and we know you wanted to go to hawaii,
所以我们让你们二者兼得了
so we decided to give you both.
信不信由你 这是Larry Bird的主意
Believe it or not, it was Larry Bird's idea.
Larry人呢
Where is Larry?
哈 哈 哈
Ho, ho, ho!
我知道孩子们今年的圣诞礼物
I understand your children had a bit of a mishap
出了点小意外
with their presents this year.
这是临时通知的 但是我也能拿到他们单子上关键的几样哦
It was short notice, but I was able to get the key items on their lists.
来 大家现在都到树跟前 我们把烛台点燃
Now gather 'round the tree, let's light up the menorah,
我们会举行宽扎庆典 直到午夜
and we'll kwanzaa till the break of dawn.
来看看有什么
Check it out.
我和你爸都知道 你特别想和朋友们去滑雪
Your dad and I know how badly you wanted to go snowboarding with your friends...
- 是滑雪   - 啥
- Snowboarding!   - Wh...
这么办吧
So here's the deal.
你现在如果马上去收拾你的东西
If you can be packed and ready to go in a couple hours,
我一会儿就开车送你去
I will personally drive you there myself.
你在开玩笑嘛
Are you kidding me?
错过这场大闹剧嘛 不可能的事儿
And miss this insanity? There's absolutely no way.
这么多年 我终于看到了这张在圣诞节应该出现的笑脸
There's the christmas face I've been hanging on to for all these years.
你欠我一个滑雪板
You owe me a snowboard.
你说这句话我还勉强能接受
And there's the one I've learned to accept.
我听说你想要一个新的平板电脑
Now, I hear you wanted the new ipad.
天啊 谢谢啦
Gee, thanks.
无线网络有点问题
The wi-fi's a bit spotty.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我只知道你是外星人
I knew you were an alien,
可我不知道原来你也是圣诞老人
but I didn't know you were also Santa Claus.
我不是真的
Oh, I'm not real...
别告诉其他人
Don't tell anyone.
这是咱俩的小秘密
It'll be our little secret.
哈 哈 哈
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Siri 谁赢了尼克队的比赛
Siri, who won the knicks game?
把未来五天的天气预报告诉我
Give me a 5-day weather forecast.
给我买一张全新的Mumfor&Sons的专辑
Buy me the new Mumford & Sons album. Ugh.
好吧 我还是去买个Kindle吧
That's it. I'm gonna get a kindle.
我受够你了
I'm done with you!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这周真的太累了
It's been a rough week.
来吧 我们去散个步
Come along. Let's go for a walk.
Siri 这身衣服会不会让我屁股显得特别大
Siri, does this suit make my ass look big?